{
    "subject": "resource/NetSuite",
    "predicate": "ontology/numberOfEmployees",
    "object": "2550",
    "human_readable": "NetSuite has 2550 employees.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6135322451591492,
            "question": "How many employees does NetSuite have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4133263826370239,
            "question": "Is NetSuite considered a large company based on its employee count?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40630361437797546,
            "question": "Could you estimate the number of departments within NetSuite given its employee count?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3799957036972046,
            "question": "How might the number of employees at NetSuite change in the future?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.375101774930954,
            "question": "Are there any publicly available resources that provide more detailed information about NetSuite's employee demographics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3593997657299042,
            "question": "What factors might influence the number of employees at a company like NetSuite?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3329845666885376,
            "question": "How does NetSuite's employee count compare to other similar companies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3186440169811249,
            "question": "What is the approximate size of NetSuite's workforce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23668904602527618,
            "question": "What are the potential implications of having a large workforce for a company like NetSuite?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19690416753292084,
            "question": "What are some strategies companies like NetSuite use to manage a large workforce effectively?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=NetSuite has 2550 employees.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4481_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the potential implications of having a large workforce for a company like NetSuite?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4481_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the approximate size of NetSuite's workforce?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4481_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does NetSuite's employee count compare to other similar companies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4481_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4481_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4481_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4481_147.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4481_151.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4481_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4481_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4481_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4481_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4481_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4481_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that none of the documents mention a specific number of employees for NetSuite, but rather mention various companies that use NetSuite and have around 30-13,000 employees."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The context information provided does not contain any direct or indirect evidence to support the statement that NetSuite has 2550 employees. The closest approximation is regarding Adobe Systems, which states it has more than 29,000 employees, and Mitchell International Inc., which has between 5000-10000 employees, neither of which supports the specific number of 2550 employees for NetSuite."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}